Karen Shearer Collection, 1935-1996, bulk 1974-1992
Indiana University Digital Library Program
- 2. Rock Chronicles (radio program), 1967-1996
  - 2.2. Rock Chronicles Publicity Materials and Photographs, 1935-1996, bulk 1980-1996
    - Fordham, Julia, undated, Publicity materials
    - Foreigner (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Forster, Robert, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Fortune (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Fossil (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Foster, David, undated, Publicity materials
    - Fountainhead (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Four Horsemen (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Fox, Britny, 1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Fox, Samantha, undated, Publicity materials
    - Foxton, Bruce, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Frampton, Peter, undated, Publicity materials
    - Frankie, undated, Publicity materials
    - Franklin, Rodney, undated, Publicity materials
    - Franks, Michael, undated, Publicity materials
    - Freewheelers (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Frey, Glenn, 1982-1985, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - From Good Homes (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Front (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Frōzen Ghōst (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Full Circle (Musical group), 1989-1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Fun Boy Three (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Fuzzbox (Musical group), 1987-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - G., Kenny, 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Gable, Eric, undated, Publicity materials
    - Gabriel, Peter, 1986-1994, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Gadd, Steve, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gaffney, Chris, undated, Publicity materials
    - Gainsburg, Serge, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gallon Drunk (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Gang of Four (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Garcia, Jerry; Jerry Garcia Band, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gary O', undated, Publicity materials
    - Gasparian, Djivan, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gear Daddies (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Geldof, Bob, 1954-, 1987-1990, Publicity materials
    - Gene Loves Jezebel (Musical group), 1986-1987, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - General Public (Musical group), 1994, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Genesis (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Georgia Satellites (Musical group), 1988-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Georgio, Andros, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Giant (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gibb, Barry, 1984, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gibb, Robin, undated, Publicity materials
    - Gifford, Kathie Lee, undated, Publicity materials
    - Gilder, Nick, undated, Publicity materials
    - Gilkyson, Eliza, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gillian, Ian & Glover, Roger, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gipsy Kings (Musical group), 1989-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Girlschool (Musical group), 1982, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Giuffria, Jeff, undated, Publicity materials
    - Glamour Camp (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Glass Tiger (Musical group), 1981-1986, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Glass, Philip, undated, Publicity materials
    - Go Go's (Musical group), 1981-1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Goats (Musical group), 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Go-Betweens (Musical group), 1988-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Godfathers (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Godley & Crème, 1981-1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gods Child (Musical group), 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Goffin, Louise, 1985-1987, Publicity materials
    - Golden Earring (Musical group), 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Goldman, Jean-Jacques, 1951-, undated, Publicity materials
    - Goo Goo Dolls (Musical group), 1995, Publicity materials
    - Goodbye Mr. Mackenzie (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gorky Park (Musical group), 1989-1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gorrie, Alan, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Grace Pool (Musical group), 1988-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Graces (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Graham, Bill, undated, Publicity materials
    - Gramm, Lou, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Grand Funk Railroad (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Grant, Amy, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Grapes of Wrath (Musical group), 1986-1991, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Grateful Dead (Musical group), 1983-1990, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Great White (Musical group), 1987-1992, 5 photographs + publicity materials
    - Grebenshchikov, Boris, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Green Day (Musical group), 1995, Publicity materials
    - Green on Red (Musical group), 1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Greenidge, Robert; Utley, Mike, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Greg Kihn Band, 1982-1984, 6 photographs + publicity materials
    - Griffin, Clive, undated, Publicity materials
    - Griffith, Nanci, undated, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Grisman, David, 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Group (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Grusin, Dave, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - GTR (Musical group), 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Guadalcanal Diary (Musical group), 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gumball (Musical group), 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Guns n' Roses (Musical group), 1987-1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Gutterboy (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Guys Next Door (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Hagar, Sammy, 1980-1987, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Haircut One Hundred (Musical group), 1982, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Haley, Bill, undated, Publicity materials
    - Hall and Oates (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hall, Denny, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hall, Lani, undated, Publicity materials
    - Hammer, Jan, 1985, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hammond, John, 1985, Publicity materials (Box 52)
    - Hampton, Bruce, vocalist; Aquarium Rescue Unit (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Hand of Fate (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Hangmen (Musical group), 1989, Publicity materials
    - Hanover (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hanover Fist (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Happy Mondays (Musical group), 1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Haran, Mary Cleeve, 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Harding, John Wesley, 1989-1992, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hardvark (Musical group), 1995, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Harlow (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Harris, Hugh, undated, Publicity materials
    - Harris, Sam, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Harrison, George, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Harrison, Jerry, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Harry, Deborah, 1986-1993, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hart, Corey, 1984-1991, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hartford, John, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hartman, Dan, 1984 October, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Harvey, Alex, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Harvey, Polly Jean, 1995, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hassel, Jon, 1990-1994, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hatchet, Molly, 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hatfield, Juliana, 1993-1995, Publicity materials
    - Hatton, Susie, 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Havalinas (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Havana Black (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Havens, Richie, undated, Publicity materials
    - Hawkins, Sophie B., 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hay, Colin, 1986-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hayes, David, undated, Publicity materials
    - Haza, Ofra, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Headpins (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hear 'N Aid (Musical group), 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Heart (Musical group), 1985-1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Heart Throbs (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Heatwave (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Heaven (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Heaven 17 (Musical group), 1980s, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Heavens Edge (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Heavy Bones (Musical group), 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hedges, Michael, undated, Publicity materials
    - Heir Apparent (Musical group), undated, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Helix (Musical group: 1974-), 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Henley, Don, 1982-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Henry Paul Band, undated, Publicity materials
    - Henry, Don, 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Henry, Joe, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Heyman, Richard X., 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Heyward, Nick, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hiatt, John, 1983-1988, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hickman, Sara, 1980s, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Himmelman, Peter, undated, Publicity materials
    - Hiroshima (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hitchcock, Russell, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hodgson, Roger, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hoenig, Michael, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hoey, Gary, 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hoffs, Susanna, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Holcomb, Robin, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hole (Musical group), 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Holland, Nicky, 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hollow Men (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Holly, Buddy, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hollyfaith (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Holmes, Rupert, 1986, Publicity materials
    - Honeymoon Suite (Musical group), 1986, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hooters (Musical group), 1985-1989, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hootie & the Blowfish (Musical group), 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Hopkins, Jerry, 1981 July, Publicity materials
    - Horn, Jim, undated, Publicity materials
    - Hornsby, Bruce; Range (Musical group), 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Horse (Musical group), 1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hot Tuna (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hothouse Flowers (Musical group), 1988-1990, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - House (Musical group), 1988-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - House of Love (Musical group), 1980s, Publicity materials
    - House of Schock (Musical group), 1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Howell, Kurt, undated, Publicity materials
    - Huayucaltia (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hue & Cry (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hugo Largo (Musical group), 1988-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Human League (Musical group), 1980s, 5 photographs + publicity materials
    - Human Radio (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hummingbirds (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Humpe Humpe (Musical group), 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hunter (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hunter, Ian, undated, Publicity materials
    - Hunter, John, undated, Publicity materials
    - Hunter, Steve (Stephen John), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hunters & Collectors (Musical group), 1983-1988, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Hurrah! (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hurricane (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Hu?sker Du? (Musical group), 1986-1987, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - I, Napoleon (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ian, Janis, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Icehouse (Musical group), 1980s, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Icicle Works (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Idle Tears (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Idol, Billy, 1993, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Iglesias, Julio, 1943-, 1983, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Illsley, John, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Imagination (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Immaculate Fools (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - In Vitro (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - India (Musician), undated, Publicity materials
    - Indigo (Musical group), 1990-1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Industry (Musical group), 1983, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Information Society (Musical group), 1988-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Insiders (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Inspiral Carpets (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Intimate Strangers (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - INXS (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - IQ (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Iris, Donnie, undated, Publicity materials
    - Iron Maiden (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Irwin, Russ, undated, Publicity materials
    - Isaak, Chris, 1985-1993, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - It Bites (Musical group), 1986-1989, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Iyall, Debora, 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jabara, Paul, 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jack Mack and the Heart Attack (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Jackson, Joe, 1954-, 1986-1989, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jagged Edge (Musical group) U.K., 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jam (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - James Brit Band, 1988, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - James, Bob, 1986-1994, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - James, Colin, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - James, Hilary; James, Bob, undated, Publicity materials
    - Jameson, Nick, undated, Publicity materials
    - Janata (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jane's Addiction (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Jarre, Jean-Michel, undated, Publicity materials
    - Jarvis, John, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jason & the Scorchers, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jeff Healey Band, 1988-1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jeffreys, Garland, 1981, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jellybean (Musical group), 1987-1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jennings, Will, 1980s, Publicity materials (Box 53)
    - Jesse's Gang, undated, Publicity materials
    - Jesus & Mary Chain (Musical group), 1988-1992, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jesus Lizard (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Jet Boys (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jethro Tull (Musical group), 1988, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jett, Joan; Black Heat (Musical group), 1983-1991, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jimmy "Z", 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jo Jo Zep (Musical group), 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jobim, Antonio Carlos, 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Joel, Billy, 1980-1989, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Johansen, David, undated, Publicity materials
    - John, Dr., 1941-, 1991-1992, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - John, Elton, 1989, 6 photographs + publicity materials
    - Johnny Hates Jazz (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Johnson, Eric, 1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Johnson, Holly, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jones, David Lynn, undated, Publicity materials
    - Jones, Howard, 1985-1989, 6 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jones, Jesus H., 1990-1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jones, Kenny, undated, Publicity materials
    - Jones, Rickie Lee, 1990-1991, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jones, Steve, 1987-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jones, Tom, 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Jones, Willi, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Journey (Musical group), 1976-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Judas Priest (Musical group), 1982, Publicity materials
    - Judy Bats (Musical group), 1990-1992, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Jungklas, Rob, 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Junk Yard Band, 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - K., Tonio, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kadison, Joshua, 1993-1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kahn, Brenda, undated, Publicity materials
    - Kajagoogoo (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Kamen, Michael, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kamen, Nick, 1986-1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Kane Gang (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kansas (Musical group), 1982-1988, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Kasem, Casey, undated, Publicity materials
    - Kass, Patricia, undated, Publicity materials
    - Katmandü (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Katrina and the Waves (Musical group), 1985-1989, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Katydids (Musical group), 1990-1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Kay, John, undated, Publicity materials
    - KBC Band, undated, Publicity materials
    - Keedy, undated, Publicity materials
    - Keel (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Keene, Tommy, 1986-1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Keezer, Geoff, 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kelly, Paul, 1955-; Messengers (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kemp, Tara, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kentucky HeadHunters (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Kershaw, Nik, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kick Axe (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Kids in the Kitchen (Musical group), 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kill for Thrills, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Killer Dwarfs, undated, Publicity materials
    - Kilzer, John, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kimmel, Tom, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - King (Musical group), 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - King Crimson (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - King Kobra (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - King of Kings (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - King Swamp (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - King, Carole, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - King, Dee Dee, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - King, Jackie, 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kingdom Come (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kings (Musical group), undated, 7 photographs + publicity materials
    - Kings of the Sun (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Kinks (Musical group), 1982-1993, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Kisor, Ryan, 1982-1993, Publicity materials
    - Kiss (Musical group), 1979-1980, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Kiss the Sky (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kitaro?, 1953-, 1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - KLF (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Knack (Musical group), 1981, Publicity materials
    - Knight, Holly, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Koreana (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Koz, Dave, undated, Publicity materials
    - Kraftwerk (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Kreator (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Krieger, Robby, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Krokus (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - KTP (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Kuepper, Ed, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - L.A. Dream Team (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - L.A. Guns (Musical group), 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Lady Pank (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Lagre?ne, Bire?li, 1966-, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Laid Back (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Laine, Paul, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Laing, Shona, undated, Publicity materials
    - Lamb, Annabel, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Lamond, George, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Landreth, Sonny, 1995, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Lanois, Daniel, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Larsen, Neil, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Larson, Nicolette, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Latin Playboys, undated, Publicity materials
    - Latin Quarter (Musical group), 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Lauper, Cyndi, 1984-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Lava Hay (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Lavole, Daniel, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Law & Order (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Le Mans (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Led Zeppelin (Musical group), 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Lee, Albert, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Lee, Alvin, undated, Publicity materials
    - Leeds, Eric, 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Lekakis, Paul, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Lemonheads (Musical group), 1992, Publicity materials
    - Lemper, Ute, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Lennon, John, 1986-1988, Publicity materials
    - Lennon, Julian, 1984, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Leo, Josh, undated, Publicity materials
    - Lesmana, Indra, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Let's Active (Musical group), 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Letters to Cleo (Musical group), 1995, Publicity materials